(Sheldon:)Because the truth made me look bad.
(Sheldon:)Whereas a ridiculous bald-faced lie
makes me look good.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, if Kripke asks...
(Sheldon:)...tell him my coitus with Amy is frequent,
intense and whimsically inventive.
(Leonard:)Is my coitus whimsically inventive?
(Penny:)That is what I write
on the bathroom walls.
"For a whimsically inventive time,
call Leonard Hofstadter."
(Leonard:)I know you're joking,
but I'd be okay with that.
(Penny:)- Sheldon, can I ask you a question?
- Of course.
Are you ever gonna sleep with Amy?
- That's awfully personal.
- We don't ask Sheldon things like that.
(Penny:)Maybe you don't, I do. What's the deal?
(Sheldon:)Well, word around the university is...
(Sheldon:)...I'm giving her sex organs
a properjostling.
(Penny:)All right, come on, be serious.
You have been going out a long time.